so about my husband all right so my
husband is a big man and is six four I'm
fine babe we breathe big kids and and we
wanted them to be in sports and when
they were growing up and so we made them
do all kinds of mess they didn't want to
do and we put our boy when he was little
bitty we put him in t-ball
he hated it I don't know if any of y'all
have had a baby play t-ball but for
those of you who don't know t-ball
season it's about a hundred and ten
degrees outside it's little children
that are for look like they've got a
diaper on under their baseball pants or
a pull-up the games last about three
hours
nobody ever hits the ball throws the
ball catches the ball makes contact with
the ball
my baby laid in a fetal position in the
outfield the entire season he never
touched a ball ever once a while he'd
pop his little head up and say one game
it was so hot
and I tell I told the middle one to go
out and take her brother a water bottle
she was about two and a half and she
went walking out there with a tutu and a
crown and a wand and her pink prostitute
she's from Walmart
she woke about half-way stomped got a
glazed look over eyes pulled her little
panties to the side and poked in the
table she really damn so I had to run
out there and get a stick and flick it
into the woods because I didn't want
another child to step in it or think it
was a milk done he would not play sports
for several years because of that trauma
and then ended up playing football and
and cross-country and a bunch of stuff
and still very he likes to mountain bike
and hike and do scary things but he
likes to come you know out west he likes
and he's a fly fisherman can y'all tell
I'm in love with him okay okay all right
about the sports I played sports I'm
wanting them to play sports - I know
y'all are thinking UCC thing you did not
but I played basketball thank you I made
that it was the early eighties when I
played and I had really big hair I used
to hot roll my hair to play ball
we all did okay so and I'm from such a
little bitty farming community and it's
500 people in Middle Tennessee and we
didn't know what waterproof mascara was
so by the end of my games I look like
say if Timmy won that now his Cooper had
a child together I was a forward
sometimes I had to be the center if Mary
down had to take her baby to the health
department my husband is very smart does
very well
we are sucking the life out of him he is
a nice-looking man but he has a receding
hairline and he hates it
I think it's handsome but he hates it so
I said why don't I take you to my
hairdresser and we'll get her to buzz
you one of those haircuts real close to
your head like Justin Timberlake you
know what I mean like real close to the
hip when we did it and we didn't know
his hand was pointed
[Music]
and he said I look like somebody and I
can't quite think of who it is
and I said is it bull on Night Court
he said no
that's not who I was thinking about
about three days later he sit on the who
it is
it's that lazy starfish Patrick on
SpongeBob Thursday thank y'all so much
for watching my special now I need you
to watch my entire special for $0.99 and
then click it and then I need you to
watch more clips and then click it and I
don't know what you're supposed to be
clicking but they tell the young people
are telling me I don't understand but
just click it